<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Be Better At Cooking In 30 Days</string>

    <string name="day1">Day 1: Get your knives sharpened</string>
    <string name="day2">Day 2: …And learn to chop an onion (for real)</string>
    <string name="day3">Day 3: Master the art of cooking rice</string>
    <string name="day4">Day 4: …and poaching eggs</string>
    <string name="day5">Day 5: Save your grease</string>
    <string name="day6">Day 6: Make pickles</string>
    <string name="day7">Day 7: Keep your scraps</string>
    <string name="day8">Day 8: Try a new spice</string>
    <string name="day9">Day 9: Ditch your aluminum skillet for cast iron</string>
    <string name="day10">Day 10: And while you\'re at it, buy bigger pots and pans</string>
    <string name="day11">Day 11: Hoard chicken breasts in bulk in your freezer</string>
    <string name="day12">Day 12: Try a totally new vegetable</string>
    <string name="day13">Day 13: Store cheese in oil</string>
    <string name="day14">Day 14: Taste as you go</string>
    <string name="day15">Day 15: Cook a new dish with your favorite food</string>
    <string name="day16">Day 16: Make your own burgers and freeze them</string>
    <string name="day17">Day 17: Cook soup from scratch</string>
    <string name="day18">Day 18: Buy soy sauce, lemons and parmesan cheese</string>
    <string name="day19">Day 19: Make your own jam</string>
    <string name="day20">Day 20: Roast those veggies</string>
    <string name="day21">Day 21: Cook something in red wine</string>
    <string name="day22">Day 22: Try a new cut of meat</string>
    <string name="day23">Day 23: Make your own bread and freeze it</string>
    <string name="day24">Day 24: Think beyond salmon</string>
    <string name="day25">Day 25: Add salt to your salads</string>
    <string name="day26">Day 26: Give grains besides quinoa a go</string>
    <string name="day27">Day 27: Add wine to your butter</string>
    <string name="day28">Day 28: Go to speciality shops instead of the grocery store</string>
    <string name="day29">Day 29: Buy a microplane</string>
    <string name="day30">Day 30: Keep dessert simple</string>

    <string name="description1">If you can’t effortlessly slice through an avocado, how the heck are you going to make avocado toast for breakfast? Most kitchen and hardware stores will do it for you—sometimes even for free.</string>
    <string name="description2">Cut off the top of the onion and save it for your compost bin. Peel off the outer layers, then chop the entire thing vertically. Next, chop those slices horizontally. Bam, you’re done.</string>
    <string name="description3">Always remember the 1:2 ratio. One part rice, two parts water. And don’t forget to add a bit of the secret ingredient before you serve it.</string>
    <string name="description4">Always crack your egg into a glass ramekin before you pour it into the water to keep the yolk from breaking. And if you’re hosting a crowd, skip the pot altogether and cook \'em in a muffin tin.</string>
    <string name="description5">Whenever you cook bacon, save the grease for later. It’ll come in handy the next time you make pancakes, or pretty much anything else you want to taste really, really good. </string>
    <string name="description6">Pickled veggies look impressive, but they’re a total cinch to make. Heat vinegar, water, kosher salt and sugar on the stove, then pour the mixture into a mason jar with sliced veggies and herbs. When it cools, pop it in the fridge and they’ll keep for three weeks.</string>
    <string name="description7">Veggie tops, bones and hard cheese rinds make a delicious soup stock. Keep them in your freezer until you’re ready to make some chicken noodle.</string>
    <string name="description8">Might we suggest turmeric, which is super tasty and extremely good for you</string>
    <string name="description9">It can withstand any temperature, it’s incredibly durable and is a great vessel for nacho dip.</string>
    <string name="description10">One thing that separates home cooks from the pros is giant pots. Use a small one and you’re at risk of overcrowding, causing your food to cook unevenly.</string>
    <string name="description11">You never know when you might need to whip up an amazing dinner in under an hour.</string>
    <string name="description12">Meet turnips. You can turn them into fries, mash them, roast them or add them to soup. And if you want to get really adventurous, expand your veggie horizons by joining a CSA.</string>
    <string name="description13">Pour oil and herbs over mozzarella, feta and goat cheese to add more flavor and make the cheese a little tastier (if that’s even possible).</string>
    <string name="description14">If the Top Chef judges have said it once, they’ve said it a million times: Continue to season and taste your food as you cook. But don’t add too much—you can always add more salt, but it’s tricky to take it away.</string>
    <string name="description15">Obsessed with cauliflower? Try cauliflower tacos. Or steak. Or just roast it whole.</string>
    <string name="description16">Whether they’re beef, turkey, salmon or veggie, make a batch and keep them on hand for weeknight dinners and surprise guests.</string>
    <string name="description17">It takes a little longer, but trust us, it’s worth it. You’ll never want to make the canned stuff again.</string>
    <string name="description18">Mark our words, these three ingredients will save almost any bland dish. Always have them on hand in your fridge for cooking emergencies.</string>
    <string name="description19">It’s a total breakfast game changer, but it takes only five minutes (yep) to make from scratch.</string>
    <string name="description20">Remember the rule about not crowding the pot? Same goes with sheet pans. Make sure there’s lots of room for your broccoli to get crispy.</string>
    <string name="description21">Might we suggest red wine pasta? It’s as delicious as it sounds.</string>
    <string name="description22">Like pork chops. Or lamb shanks. Or sirloin roast. Or liver. (OK, maybe not liver.)</string>
    <string name="description23">You can have fresh flatbread for dinner every night for the next two weeks.</string>
    <string name="description24">Try your hand at scallops, cod, mussels or tuna. Anything but salmon, really. (Chefs think it’s boring.)</string>
    <string name="description25">It sounds simple, but it’s the secret ingredient that makes all of the flavors come together. It’s basically the difference between a mish-mosh and a meal.</string>
    <string name="description26">So you’ve really gotten into cooking quinoa instead of rice. Awesome—but now it’s time to broaden your horizons and try amaranth. It’s just as healthy and tasty, we promise. </string>
    <string name="description27">Because nothing says “I’m a freaking amazing cook” like fancy compound butter.</string>
    <string name="description28">Yep, the big-box store is convenient, but if you buy at specialty cheese and meat shops, you’ll support local businesses and get a fresher and larger selection. Win-win.</string>
    <string name="description29"> …And use it to casually grate fresh Parm on your guests’ plates after you serve them.</string>
    <string name="description30">After spending hours in the kitchen, remember that a bowl of fresh fruit and whipped cream can be just as tasty as a soufflé. Now sit back and relax, chef.</string>

    <string name="expand_description">tap to expand description</string>
    <string name="top_bar_title">Cook better in 30 days</string>
</resources>